<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sebastiaan Westheim on Westhes</title><link>https://westhes.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Sebastiaan Westheim on Westhes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Sebastiaan Westheim</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 09:48:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://westhes.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pathfinding</title><link>https://westhes.github.io/projects/project-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 09:48:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://westhes.github.io/projects/project-2/</guid><description>WIP
A* pathfinding Github - Pathfinding Variants
Modified Depth-First search algorithm with heuristic iterating over a few paths.</description></item><item><title>Procedural terrain generation</title><link>https://westhes.github.io/projects/project-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 09:48:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://westhes.github.io/projects/project-1/</guid><description>Like many around my age, I grew up when minecraft was still a brand new thing.
Inspired by it&amp;rsquo;s grand and amazing worlds I wanted to create something like it for the longest time. During one of my courses at Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences (AUAS) we were tasked to create a procedurally generated object. While this was only meant to be a simple object, I quickly became invested in this technology.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://westhes.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://westhes.github.io/about/</guid><description>Background Back in 2011 a younger me pondered about his future, wondering what he would do after finishing college. At the time I had yet to know that a path of game-development and software-engineering lay ahead of me.
In 2012 I made my first steps towards becoming a game-developer by studying game development at the Grafisch lyceum Rotterdam. Over the course of 4 years this would be my introduction to programming, modeling, and various other software skills.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://westhes.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://westhes.github.io/contact/</guid><description>In case you would like to contact me, you can reach me through one of the following channels:
Platform URL Github https://github.com/Westhes LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastiaan-westheim/</description></item></channel></rss>